Amanda Seals Show. It's Amanda Seals here, and it is time for another...
Ivy Nuttin'!
So we've been talking about Valentine's Day and, you know, it's Valentine's Day week.
It was our group chat topic of the week and the conversation around love.
And one of our callers said something that I just thought was really impactful, and she said,
you know, I really wish that Valentine's Day, especially for the Black community,
was more about celebrating our love for each other versus, like, romantic love,
because that's something that we really need to, like, step into.
And I think that is so true.
And I think we can also extend it to, like, our love for ourselves.
There's really a discussion to be had about what really is love.
How do you show love to each other?
How do you show love to yourself?
How do you show love to your community?
You know, how do you see your parents show love?
How do you see your friends show love?
Like, the discussion of really what love is.
And I think that's something that's so missing from our society.
We perform love, you know, we behave in what we think is the act of love,
but truly, do we understand it?
It's not really something we're taught.
It's something we hear in Keith Sweat songs,
and we're not really sure if that's love or whining.
So, there you have it.
That is my...